<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Balashov Artem</title>
    <link>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Balashov Artem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Technological stresses  of integral constructions</title>
      <link>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/scienific/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/scienific/</guid>
      <description>Design of stiffened composite panels with account process technological deformation.
 Goals Introduction Analytic model FEA Experimental model Source code Conclusion
  Goals The main purpose if to make an analytic model to considering technological deflected mode (Stress-Strain condition, or SSC) while design an integral structure. (By intagral means structure, that made from 2 or more parts and formed at the same time).
First step objectives: * Investigation influence of structural parameters integral construction on technological deflected mode in terms of stringer set panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatization of Abaqus FEA using python</title>
      <link>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/automatization-of-abaqus-fea-using-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/automatization-of-abaqus-fea-using-python/</guid>
      <description>In this paper I will describe how to automate Abaqus Finite Element Analyses using python script on example of optimization plain panel from composite material under equal pressure distribution.
Contents  Introduction Initial data Work in GUI  Modeling CM Loads and BC Result export  Scripts generation and formatting Main file adjustment
 Making template Parsing result file Iteration optimization Main file optimization  Conclusion
  Introduction The main point of this whole work is to replace action sequence in GUI by formatted scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA-156 Wing skin</title>
      <link>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/la-156_wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://balashov-artem.github.io/Portfolio/projects/la-156_wing/</guid>
      <description>Design of an LA-156 Wing skin.
Contents  Introduction Work scheme Input data Parametrize Master-Geometry Calculating  Pressure type allocation Adhesive connection Skin types comprasion Figurativly parts  Modeling FEM calculation Technology and manufacturing  Segments lining Modling frame Materials and equipment list  Conclusion Tech-documentation  Introduction The aim of this work was a design of covering for the wing LA-156, as a part of acomplex teamwork. The operation loads of the skin panels were calculated based on the rationing loads of the wing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>